Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/taha-ahmed-siddiqui-9615bb84 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Android Development Networking Software Development

Taha Ahmed Siddiqui

Assistant Application Consultant at Euronet Pakistan (Private) Limited

Pakistan

Summary

Experience in "OPERATIONS AND CUSTOMER SUPPORT" in Banking / Card/ Payment System.

Responsible to daily operations. Daily processes of clearing, settlements incoming, outgoing, reconciliations process and back office support in financial operation services. To improve the routine basis tasks and learning in payment sector to increase the core skills in operations and development side.

Also provide the Level 1 and Level 2 support to customer (Member Banks) facing systems issues and issues with Financial / Non-Financial Transactions of ATM / POS Acquiring, configuration levels, Transactions of Settlements, EFT (Electronic Fund Transfer), POS Terminal Applications, IBFT, CMS (Card Management System), Card Operations of service levels, EOD Process and Provide escalated, highly complex technical support to customers by investigating and resolving system related matters.

Experience

Euronet Pakistan (Private) Limited 4 years 2 months

Assistant Application Consultant March 2021 - Present (1 year 1 month) Pakistan

Associate System Engineer February 2018 - March 2021 (3 years 2 months) karachi

OAT Sol
Co-Founder
September 2017 - Present (4 years 7 months)

Education

usman institute of technology
Bachelor of Science (BS), Computer Programming, Specific
Applications · (2013 - 2017)

greenland public school matriculation · (2005 - 2007)